Last updated: _May 30, 2017_

**MY-SEARCH.COM PRIVACY POLICY**

Thank you for visiting our website. Your privacy is important to us, and we have adopted this Privacy Policy to memorialize our data collection, use and disclosure practices for our website at www.my-search.com, along with its related tools and services (the “Website”). The Website is owned and operated by Pinch of Awesome, LP (“we,” “us” or “our”).  This Privacy Policy applies to anyone using or viewing our Website and to information provided to us via the Website by visitors, customers or users of our Website (“users,” “you” or “your”). However, it does not apply to information collected from our employees, contractors or vendors, or from anyone via any hard copy communications.

1. **CONSENT**

By using or accessing any part of the Website, including without limitation all content available through the Website, you consent to this Privacy Policy.  If you do not agree with any provision of this Privacy Policy, you may not use or access the Website.

Information collected through the Website may be transferred, used and stored in the United States and in foreign jurisdictions in which we, our users, or our agents for the Website are located now or at any time in the future. If you access the Website, you consent to the capture, storage, transfer, use and processing of your Personal Information (as defined below) in and between all of those jurisdictions.  The data protection and other laws in some countries and jurisdictions (such as the Federal laws and some State laws in the United States) are not as comprehensive or stringent as the privacy laws in other countries and jurisdictions (such as the laws of the European Union).  You agree that all transactions relating to our Website shall be deemed to have occurred in the United States, where we currently have all of our personnel and operations.

2. **COLLECTION OF INFORMATION; THIRD PARTY SITES**

We may collect Personal Information in connection with our Website. You may always choose not to provide Personal Information, but this may prevent you from receiving certain services. When we use the term “Personal Information,” we mean information that can be used to identify an individual and may include your full or partial first and last name, postal business or home address, electronic email address, user ID, password, telephone number, and fax number.

Our Website may not be used or accessed by individuals under the age of 18 (or the age of majority in your jurisdiction of residence or from where you are accessing the Website where 18 is not the age of majority).  However, in the event that our Website is improperly accessed by any users under the age of majority in violation of our terms and conditions, the Website does not intentionally collect any Personal Information from such individuals, nor do we authorize or want such information to be provided to us.  If we learn that we have inadvertently collected Personal Information from a user under the age of majority, upon receipt of notice from a parent or guardian of such user, we will delete that user’s Personal Information and/or disable such information from being viewed or accessed by any other user or other third party.

We may also collect “Non-Personal Information” about you.  “Non-Personal Information” means information that is not Personal Information, including, without limitation, aggregated and anonymized information.  Examples of the Non-Personal Information we may collect include, but are not limited to: your IP address; your search queries; information about your operating system and browser (such as maker and version); information, content or advertisements you view, hover over or click on; and city and state (but not precise geographic location) in which you are located.  We will not use Non-Personal Information to try to identify you, and if we associate any Non-Personal Information with information that personally identifies you, then we will treat it as Personal Information.  We may also use the data we collect to determine which search engines to direct your queries to through our custom search feature, and to determine compensation under our arrangements with our search provider partners and other companies. 

We may also share web log information with our search provider partners and other partners so that they can deliver relevant results in response to your search queries.

Information from our Website may be collected by us or by one of our service providers but in either case, this Privacy Policy will govern the collection, use and sharing of that information.

The Website contains third party content and links to third party websites and other materials, including without limitation videos, images, graphics, audio and text.  Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy policies, practices, or content of websites or materials owned by others that may link to or that may be linked from or integrated with the Website (Third Party Sites”).  Accordingly, we encourage you to review the privacy policies and terms of use of Third Party Sites so that you understand how those websites collect, use and share your Personal Information.

3. **USE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

Pinch of Awesome, LP may use Personal or Non-Personal Information to improve online operations; process transactions you initiate; provide customer service; provide newsletters and/or other communications or services which you have signed up for or otherwise agreed to receive; display advertising and other content that is customized to your apparent interests or preferences; send account- or transaction-related communications; perform research and analysis aimed at improving our products, service and technologies; and manage our systems.  We may also use this information for internal purposes to help us diagnose problems, monitor traffic patterns and otherwise continually improve our Website and related services.

Please note that when you initially sign up or submit information on our Website, you may receive email messages or newsletters from us. You will be given the opportunity, in any commercial e-mail that we send to you, to opt out of receiving such messages in the future by using the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of each such communication or contacting us by email. It may take up to 10 business days for us to fully process an unsubscribe request, and we may send you other types of transactional and relationship email communications, such as requests for additional information, confirmations, service updates or announcements, and administrative notices without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.

4. **DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

We may disclose Personal Information and Non-Personal Information about you to companies, agents, contractors, service providers or others engaged to perform functions on our behalf (such as processing payments, providing data storage, hosting the Website, conducting audits and performing web analytics, and fulfilling orders that you initiate), and to market other Pinch of Awesome, LP products and services to you (for example, to send you messages concerning new Website features or special offers).

We may also disclose your Personal Information to third parties, in our sole discretion, to: (a) enforce or apply the terms and conditions of the Website, including investigations of potential violations thereof; (b) comply with legal or regulatory requirements or a governmental request; (c) protect the rights, property or safety of Pinch of Awesome, LP, other users or other third parties; (d) comply with a request by any authority, such as a police department or regulatory authority; or (e) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical problems that may arise. We may also disclose Non-Personal Information to our clients, developers, business partners, merchants, advertisers, investors, potential buyers and other third parties for any reason in our sole discretion.

Pinch of Awesome, LP reserves the right to transfer information (including your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information) to a third party in the event of a reorganization, spin-out, sale, merger, or transfer of some or all of the assets of our company, or in the unlikely event of a bankruptcy, liquidation or receivership of our business. However, we will provide you with advance written notice in the event any such transfer would subject your Personal Information to materially different privacy practices.

5. **CHOICE; ACCESSING AND UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION**

When you use our Website, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your Personal Information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes.  We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backups), or for which access is not otherwise required.  In any case, where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. For information about your choices regarding targeted advertising from third party advertising networks, please see Section 6 below.

Please e-mail us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.my-search.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or contact us at the address stated below with any questions if you need assistance accessing or changing your Personal Information or if you would like to have your Personal Information deleted from our servers.  Please be aware that if you delete your Personal Information, you may not be able to continue to use the Website.  If you ask us to delete your Personal Information, we may in our sole discretion retain certain information, including your Personal Information, to satisfy our legal, audit and/or dispute resolution requirements. We may also retain your Non-Personal Information indefinitely.

6. **COOKIES AND AUTOMATIC DATA COLLECTION; ADVERTISING NETWORKS**

Non-Personal Information (including aggregate, technical or demographic information) can also be collected through the standard operation of our internet servers and logs as well as other automatic data collection tools such as “cookies” and other similar technologies.  A “cookie” is a small text file that is recorded either temporarily or persistently on your hard drive and that a website can use in order to recognize visitors who revisit the website so as to facilitate their ongoing access to and use of the website.  Information we may collect through cookies and other similar technologies includes your browser type, language preference, operating system, referring website (if applicable), the name and type of your computer or mobile device, the operating system of your device, your general geographic location, the date and time of each user visit or request, and the Website endpoints that you accessed or visited during your use of the Website.  In addition to other uses as described in this Privacy Policy, we may gather the information we collect from each user and perform statistical analysis of the aggregated information, including analysis about the behavior of visitors to our Website on an aggregated, anonymous basis.

Any Non-Personal information we collect from you through the use of our cookies, web beacons and other technologies may also be used by us and/or shared with our affiliated companies to target content and advertising to you on the Website. We may also allow unaffiliated third-party companies such as advertising networks to serve ads and/or collect anonymous, Non-Personal Information when you visit our Website. These unaffiliated third-party companies may collect and use Non-Personal Information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) in order to provide relevant content or advertisements that are likely to be of greater interest to you. This collection and use of Non-Personal Information would be governed by unaffiliated third-party companies’ own privacy policies. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacons to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).  Please note that if you delete your cookies or use a different browser, a different computer, or other device, you will need to opt out of this type of advertising again.

You may prevent our use of cookies to collect Non-Personal information about you by adjusting the option that is available in most web browsers to deny or accept cookies.  Recognize, however, that cookies may be necessary in order to provide certain features such as the customized delivery of certain information to you.

7. **INFORMATION SECURITY**

We utilize a number of reasonable information security measures to safeguard your Personal Information.  Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet and no method of data storage can be guaranteed to be secure.  Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we do not guarantee its security.

8. **YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

A California resident who has provided Personal Information to a business with whom she or he has established a business relationship for personal, family, or household purposes (“California Customer”) is entitled to request information about whether the business has disclosed her or his Personal Information to any third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. In general, if the business has made such a disclosure of Personal Information, upon receipt of a request by a California Customer, the business is required to provide a list of all third parties to whom Personal Information was disclosed in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of Personal Information that were disclosed.

Currently, we do not intend to share your Personal Information with third parties for their own direct marketing purposes.

Please note that whenever you choose to share your Personal Information with a third party or to allow your Personal Information to be shared with a third party to communicate with you, your information will be subject to the third party’s privacy policy.  If you later decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact the third party directly, as we have no control over how third parties use your Personal Information and other information.  You should always review the privacy policy of any party that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle your information.

California Customers may request further information about our compliance with California’s privacy law by e-mailing [\[email protected\]](https://www.my-search.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or contacting us as stated below.  Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer per year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this e-mail address.

9. **CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

Pinch of Awesome, LP may modify or update this Privacy Policy periodically by posting an updated policy on the Website.  You can always check the “last updated” date at the top of this document to see when the Privacy Policy was last changed.  We may also post a notice of changes to this Privacy Policy on our website when there are material changes to the policy.  We encourage you to check this Privacy Policy from time to time.

Your continued use of the Website following the effective date of an updated Privacy Policy constitutes your consent to the contents of such policy. However, we will not apply any material changes retroactively to any information we collected from you before such changes took effect, without provide notice to you.  IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO FUTURE CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST STOP USING THE WEBSITE AFTER THE EFFECTIVE DATE OF SUCH CHANGES.  Please note that upon discontinuing your use of the Website, any Privacy Policy in effect immediately prior to your departure shall continue to be binding on you and applicable to the data (including any Personal Information) collected from you prior to such departure.

10. **CONTACT US**

To ask questions about our Privacy Policy, obtain more information, or to lodge a complaint, contact us at:

Pinch of Awesome, LP

Attn: Office of the General Counsel

600 N 2nd Street  
Suite 401  
Harrisburg, PA 17101

E-Mail: [\[email protected\]](https://www.my-search.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
